这是新闻追击
This is Media Break.
给我们三分钟 我们会为你带来世界的大事
You give us three minutes and we'll give you the world.
大家早，我是卡西黄，她是帕金斯
Good morning. I'm Casey Wong with Jesse Perkins.
主要新闻，比勒陀利亚
Top story, Pretoria.
今天南非的核子冲突威胁升级
The threat of nuclear confrontation in South Africa escalated today
这个被占领的首都军人政府…
when the ruling white military government
展示一枚法国制造的中子弹
of that besieged city-state unveiled a French-made neutron bomb
并表示会使用它
and affirmed its willingness to use the three megaton device
作为该市的最后防线
as the city's last line of defense.
总统在星球大战的和平平台上
And the President's first press conferencefrom the Star Wars
举行的首个记者招待会…
got off to a shaky start,orbiting peace platform
因为电源中断而出师不利 导致总统和他的随从
when power failed causing a brief, but harmless, period of weightlessness
出现无序状态
for the visiting President and his staff.
我们稍后会回来
We'll be back in a moment.
是该做个手术的时候了吗？
Is it time for that big operation?
这可能是你一生中最重要的决定
This may be the most important decision of your life.
所以来家庭心脏中心 跟我们合格的医生…
So come down and talk to one of our qualified surgeons
详谈一下吧
here at the Family Heart Center.
家庭心脏中心
我们有延森雅马哈制造的各种心脏
We feature the complete Jarvik line, series 7 Sports Heart by Jensen, Yamaha.
可供阁下挑选
You pick the heart.
延长保养，财务安排
Extended warranties, financing.
符合申请保健税扣税
Qualifies for health tax credit.
提供请即查询
记着，我们关怀你
And remember, we care.
三名警员死亡，一名重伤
Three dead police officers, one critically injured.
警方高层指责普及消费者产品公司
Police union leaders blame Omni Consumer Products, OCP,
底特律警察局
OCP最近跟市政府达成协议
the firm which recently entered into a contract with the city
经营及管理底特律市警务处
to fund and run the Detroit Metropolitan Police Department.
OCP总裁迪克琼斯
Dick Jones, Division President, OCP.
每个警员都明白
Every policeman knows when he joins the force
迪克琼斯 - OCP高级总裁
他们的工作有一定的危险
that there are certain inherent risks that come with the territory.
不信的话，可以问他们
Ask any cop, he'll tell you,
若你不能承受压力，还是不要干好了
"if you can't stand the heat, you better stay out of the kitchen."
法兰克警员负伤逃命
Although seriously wounded, Officer Frank Frederickson escaped
并且认出这个人
and identified this man.
底特律旧城区的 黑帮首领鲍迪克来伦…
Clarence Boddicker, unofficial crime boss of Old Detroit.
涉嫌与31名警员之死有关
Now sought in connection with the deaths of 31 police officers.
目前他正消遥法外
Today, he's at large,
而福特医院的医生们…
while doctors at Henry Ford Memorial Hospital
正在抢救法兰克警员
fight to save the life of Officer Frank Frederickson.
法兰克，祝你好运
Good luck, Frank.
底特律市西区警署
企图谋杀？他没有杀人
Attempted murder? It's not like he killed someone.
这侵犯我当事人的公民权益
This is a clear violation of my client's civil rights.
改控袭击我就马上可以付保释金
Make it aggravated assault, and I can make bail, in cash, now.
你的当事人是个混蛋 你也是个混蛋
Listen, pal, your client's a scumbag, you're a scumbag,
混蛋们要见法官的
and scumbags see the judge on Monday morning!
快离开我的警察局 还要带走那个小子
Now get out of my police station, and take laughing boy with you!
给我过来！
Get over there!
你有权保持沉默，了解吗？
You have the right to remain silent. Do you understand me?
了解
Sure, sure.
- 被抓过吗？ - 没有
- Priors? - No.
你好
Hi.
摩菲，从南区调派来的
Uh, Murphy. Transferring in from Metro South.
不错的警察局
Nice precinct.
是的
Yeah, pretty good.
你在这里，靠工作维生吧 拿你的装备吧
We work for a living down here, Murphy. Get your armor and suit up.
请带我回家
Please take me home!
现在不行，去拿杯咖啡
Not now, E.J. Get a cup of coffee.
警官
Oh, Sarge.
史达，法兰克有消息吗？
Stark, is there any word on Frederickson?
仍然不容乐观
They're still listing him as critical.
他老婆一定会发疯了
His wife must be going out of her mind.
- 摩菲？ - 是的
- Murphy, huh? - Yeah, that's me.
- 文森 - 你好
- Manson. - Hi.
什么让你来到这里的？
What brings you to this little paradise?
OCP调派了很多新人来这里
Beats me, man. I think OCP's moving a lot of new guys up here.
普及消费者产品，一群笨蛋
Omni Consumer Products. What a bunch of morons.
他们会把这个部门搞得一团糟的
They're gonna manage this department right into the ground!
- 你从哪里来的？ - 南区
- Where are you from? - Metro South.
欢迎来到地狱
Welcome to hell.
- 摩菲？ - 在
- Murphy. - Yo.
消减了东区十个人
You cut 10 guys loose over on the east side.
有麻烦时才增加人手
You try to get backup when you're in a jam.
你遇上麻烦后才找救兵
Yeah, try to get a medevac after you've been jammed.
我告诉你我们该做什么，就是罢工
I'll tell you what we should do. We should strike. Fuck 'em!
法兰克
天啊！
Oh, boy.
丧礼明天举行
The funeral's tomorrow.
部门要求所有休假警员出席
The department requests all officers not on duty to attend.
所有奠仪按照惯例交给西素
Any donations for the family may be given to Cecil as usual.
我不要再听到罢工的言论
And I don't want to hear any more talk about strike!
我们不是水管工，我们是警务人员
We're not plumbers. We're police officers.
警务人员是不罢工的
And police officers don't strike.
摩菲，出动
Murphy, front and center.
摩菲
好威猛！
Hello, tiger.
耶！
Oh, yes!
陆逸斯，你处理完那个嫌犯就过来
Lewis, come here when you're finished fucking around with your suspect.
振作一点！
Get on your feet!
这是你的新伙伴
This guy's gonna be your new partner.
摩菲，这是陆逸斯，带他到附近看看
Murphy, meet Lewis. Show him the neighborhood.
很高兴认识你
Glad to know you, Murphy.
身手不错
Pretty neat.
你还不认识路线，还是我来开车吧
I better drive until you know your way around.
通常我在了解我的新伙伴时 都是我开车的
I usually drive when I'm breaking in a new partner.
你认为那个老头会在场？
You really think the old man is gonna be there?
为何邀请我们？
Why would they invite us?
所有部门主管都带了支援队来了
All division heads are bringing their support teams.
这是件大事
It's big.
他们会通过三角洲城计划
I figure they're green-lighting Delta City.
不可能，他们从不提前行事的
What, are you kidding? They never do anything ahead of schedule.
琼斯已经准备好209系列，想夸耀一番
It's Jones. He's got the 209 series online and now he wants to show off.
真棘手
That's a tough break, Bob.
什么？
What? What?
ED209出现严重延误时…
Well, ED 209 ran into serious delays and cost overruns.
老头下令要有后备计划
The old man ordered a backup plan.
95楼，祝君愉快
95th floor. Have a nice day.
可能想挫挫琼斯的锐气吧
Probably just to light a fire under Jones' ass.
- 对 - 老鲍伯获得那个任务
- Yeah? - Old Bob here gets the assignment.
然后呢？
Yeah.
保安概念部的人都不以篇然
Nobody in Security Concepts takes it seriously.
该死的琼斯！ 我可以的话也会直接找老头
It's a better plan. Fucking Jones! I'd go straight to the Old Man if I could.
别跟琼斯作对
Don't mess with Jones, man. He'll make sushi out of you.
小心，听说他不是好惹的
Yeah, you better be careful, man. I heard Jones is a real shark.
- 笨蛋，谁问过你？ - 鲍伯
- Who asked you, twerp? - Bob.
警方有什么问题？
What about this police thing, what's the problem?
自从我们接手后 他们的工会一直捣乱
Their union's been bitching ever since we took over.
一如往常
You know, the usual nonsense.
但我们会扭转局势的
We'll turn things around.
好，很好，我们开始吧
Mmm-hmm. Good, very good. Let's get started.
各位朋友
Now, friends,
十多年来我一直有这个梦想
I've had this dream for more than a decade now.
一个我邀请各位一起分享的梦想
A dream which I've invited you all to share with me.
六个月后我们会开始兴建三角洲城
In six months, we begin construction of Delta City.
在现在底特律旧城的位置
Where Old Detroit now stands.
老城有一个弊病
Old Detroit has a cancer.
就是犯罪问题
The cancer is crime.
在我们雇用二百万名工人…
And it must be cut out before we employ the 2 million workers
在城里大兴土木前一定要制止它
that will breathe life into this city again.
对
Yes.
调整税制已经为机构
Although shifts in the tax structure
创造理想的经营环境
have created an economy ideal for corporate growth,
但社会服务，也就是指执行法规…
community services, in this case law enforcement,
却受到损害
have suffered.
我认为我们是时候回馈社会了
I think it's time we gave something back.
迪克
Dick.
细心看看本公司的以前的成绩
Take a close look at the track record of this company.
各位就会知道我们曾经冒险…
And you'll see that we have gambled in markets
投资在被视为无利可图的市场
traditionally regarded as nonprofit.
医院、监狱、太空探索
Hospitals, prisons, space exploration.
我认为商机无限
I say good business is where you find it.
我们现在有合约
As you know, we've entered into a contract with the city
可在本地执行法规
to run local law enforcement.
但对于安保概念…
But at Security Concepts,
相信一支有效率的警队 只是解决问题的一部分
we believe an efficient police force is only part of the solution.
我们需要更多的东西
No. We need something more.
我们需要一个24小时当班的警察
We need a 24-hour-a-day police officer.
一个不用吃、不用睡觉的警察
A cop that doesn't need to eat or sleep.
一个配备强劲火力和反应敏锐的警察
A cop with superior firepower and the reflexes to use it.
各位同事…
Fellow executives,
我诚意为大家介绍 执行法纪的未来精英
it gives me great pleasure to introduce you to the future of law enforcement.
ED209
执法机械人209系列 是个自给自足的执法机械人
The Enforcement Droid series 209 is a self-sufficient law enforcement robot.
209被设定保卫市区安宁
209 is currently programmed for urban pacification,
但那只是个开始
but that is only the beginning.
经过一次到旧城区出巡后…
After a successful tour of duty in Old Detroit,
我们可以预期209会成为 未来十年热门的军用产品
we can expect 209 to become the hot military product for the next decade.
- 麦菲马纳博士 - 我们需要一个目标
- Dr. McNamara. - We'll need an arrest subject. - Mr. Kinney. - Yes, sir?
你可否帮个忙？
Would you come up and give us a hand, please?
好的
Yes, sir.
肯尼先生会帮我们模拟一次 典型的拘捕和缴械过程
Mr. Kinney is going to help us simulate a typical arrest and disarming procedure.
肯尼先生，用你的枪作威吓状
Mr. Kinney, use your gun in a threatening manner.
- 指着ED209 - 好的
- Point it at Ed 209. - Yes, sir.
请你放下武器，你有20秒时间
Please put down your weapon. You have 20 seconds to comply.
你还是依它的话做吧
I think you'd better do what he says, Mr. Kinney.
你还有15秒时间
You now have 15 seconds to comply.
- 你触犯了刑法第113条第9节 - 切断电源
- You are in direct violation... - Cut the power! Pull the board! ...of Penal Code 113, Section 9.
你还有五秒时间
You now have five seconds to comply.
救我！
Help! Help me!
- 四、三、二、一 - 救我，救命！
Four, three, two, one.
我现在有权使用武力
I am now authorized to use physical force.
太恐怖了
It's horrible.
要叫急救人员吗？
Somebody want to call a goddamn paramedic?
琼森，我们走吧 这件事就此了结！
- Let's go, Johnson! - You pull the plug on this thing!
不要碰他
All right, don't touch him.
不要碰他！
Don't touch him!
它听不到丢下枪的声音
He didn't hear the gun drop.
它听不到？
He didn't hear it?
天啊
Oh, God.
迪克，我很失望
Dick, I'm very disappointed.
只是小故障，暂时失灵罢了
I'm sure it's only a glitch, a temporary setback.
你叫这做小故障？
You call this a glitch?
我们在六个月内就动工了
We're scheduled to begin construction in six months.
这个故障会害苦我们 单是利息就损失5千万
Your temporary setback could cost us $50 million in interest payments alone.
不必的
Not necessarily, sir.
有个机器战警计划
Perhaps you're aware of the Robocop program
是我研究出来应变这种事故的
developed by myself at Security Concepts as a contingency against just this sort of thing.
感谢你的关心
Thank you for your concern, Mr. Morton.
我们可以…
I'm sure this is something we can take up in my office...
等一会，迪克！
Now, wait a minute. Dick!
我要出去！
Get me out of here!
我们可能要重新估计了
Maybe what we need here is a fresh perspective.
说说你的计划，需要多久的时间？
Tell me about your plan, Mr. Morton. How long will it take?
我们正在进行
We're ready to go, sir.
我们调派了一些合适人选重组警务处
We've restructured the police department and placed prime candidates according to risk factor.
我们九十天内可以制出样本
I'm confident that we can go to prototype within 90 days.
很好，召集你的手下
Good, very good. Get your staff together, Mr. Morton.
二十分钟后开会作介绍
I'll expect a full presentation in 20 minutes.
谢谢你
Thank you, sir.
这才是取胜之道
Yes! Now, that's how it's done in the big leagues, Johnson.
抓紧机会，全力以赴
You see an opening, you go for it.
你小心点，琼斯会对付你的
You better watch your back, Bob. Jones is going to come looking for you.
去他的，他弄得一塌糊涂 我只是收拾残局罢了
Fuck Jones. He fumbled the ball and I was there to pick it up.
肯尼真是不幸
Too bad about Kinney.
那是大城市常见的事
That's life in the big city.
我们何时开始？
When do we start?
找到个蠢蛋自愿者就行
As soon as some poor schmuck volunteers.
3509单位，请到河街和葛兰街
Unit 3509, proceed to Hall and Grand.
收到，我们马上出发
Roger, we're on our way.
身手不错呢
Pretty fancy moves, Murphy.
我儿子看这个叫TJ里查的 警匪电视节目
Yeah, my son, Jimmy, watches this cop show, TJ Lazer,
里查杀死坏人时就做这个动作
and this Lazer guy does this every time he takes down a bad guy.
我儿子认为每个好警察…
So naturally, my kid thinks every good cop should be...
你不想令他失望吧
And you don't want to disappoint him.
以身作则对孩子是很重要的
Yeah, well, role models can be very important to a boy.
对，我也有同感
Okay, okay, I get a kick out of it.
所有单位，第九区…
All units, all units, sector 9.
- 那是… - 211正在途中
- That's for. .. -211 in progress.
你来开车吧
Why don't you drive?
…疑犯持有枪械，属高度危险人物
...the suspects are armed and considered dangerous.
该死！
Shit.
我不能相信
I don't believe it!
什么？
What?
你竟然烧那些钱
You burned the fucking money!
我要把门炸开！
I had to blow the door. What do you want?
它是有记号的，混蛋
It's as good as marked, you asshole!
你这个笨蛋！
You stupid, stupid asshole!
- 克来伦！ - 你想怎样？
- Clarence! - What? What do you want?
有警察跟踪我们
We got a cop on our tail.
来，开快点！快点！
Come on, man, speed it up! Move it!
我们敌不过警察的
This crate ain't gonna outrun a cop.
- 开慢点 - 你疯了吗？
- Slow down, then. - What, are you crazy, man?
闭嘴，做吧！照做！
Shut the fuck up and do it! Just do it!
这是154，我们正追截疑匪
Central, this is 154. We're in pursuit of 211 suspect.
请派人支援
Request backup.
收到，154
Roger, 154.
- 暂时没有支持 - 把你的枪给我
- Backup currently unavailable. - Give me your piece.
支持15分钟后赶到
Backup E.T.A., 15 minutes.
波比，打开门
Bobby, get the door!
大家上子弹
Everybody load up!
来吧
All right, let's go. Come on!
- 好的 - 好，我们来吧
- Okay. - All right, here we go.
现在
Now.
怎么了？他去了哪里？
What the fuck? Where did he go?
阿苗！
Emil?
他在这边！
Here! He's up here!
他在旁边
He's on the side.
他在这里
He's over here!
射他！
Get him!
克来伦，我的脚
Shit, Clarence, my leg!
利昂，扶起他
Leon, pick him up.
- 准备了吗？ - 不，等一会
- Ready? - No, hang on.
波比
Bobby.
- 波比，你会飞吗？ - 克来伦，不要！
- Can you fly, Bobby? - Clarence, no!
快点
Hit it!
不！
No!
这是154
Central, this is unit 154.
在3D区找到那辆车
We located that van by the old mill in Sector 3D.
- 支援的人呢？ - 暂时没有
- Now, where is that backup? - Backup is still unavailable.
不会吧
Oh, man!
估计在10分钟后才到达
We estimate 10 minutes before units can arrive.
你决定吧
Well, you call it.
- 我们来吧 - 好的
- Let's do it. - Okay.
去
Go.
保持联络
Stay in touch.
别动
Freeze.
举高手
Okay, let's see those hands.
慢慢来
Nice and easy.
好的
Sure.
让我拉上裤链吧？
Mind if I zip this up?
我们打劫银行，但从不留下赃款
We keep robbing banks, but we never get to keep the money.
钱滚钱
Takes money to make money.
我们偷钱买毒品
We steal money to buy coke,
然后卖出毒品赚大钱
then sell the coke to make even more money.
资金投资
Capital investment, man.
何必费神？偷回来就是了
Yeah, why bother making it when we can just steal it?
没有方法比偷东西这种自由贸易更好
Ain't no better way to steal money than free enterprise.
吸烟吗？
- Smoke? - No.
不，这些东西会害死你的
- You know, those things will kill you. - Yeah.
你想长命百岁？
You want to live forever?
比西比
Bixby!
好大的蛋糕啊！哇！
What a cake! Oh, boy!
嘿
Hey.
别动
Don't move.
开枪吧
Go ahead and do it.
不管生死，你也要束手就擒
Dead or alive, you're coming with me.
陆逸斯？
Lewis. Lewis!
陆逸斯，我这里有状况
Lewis, I got a situation here, girl.
好了，老兄，站起来！
Okay, tough guy, get up. Get up!I
转身，分开双腿，对了
Turn around. Spread your legs. That's right.
陆逸斯，你在哪里？没事吧？
Lewis, where are you? You all right?
双手放头上，陆逸斯？
Put your hands on your head. Lewis?
阿苗，我们来吧
Why don't you let us take over from here, Emil?
- 你死定了 - 不！
- Your ass is mine. - No.
等一会
Not yet it ain't.
我们抓到什么？
Well, what have we here?
老哥，你是个好警察吧？
You a good cop, hotshot?
当然是了
Sure you are.
你一定是个了不起的警察 独个儿来这里
Why, you got to be some kind of great cop to come in here all by yourself.
你的伙伴在哪里？
Where's your partner?
大伙儿，另一个在楼上
Well, guys, the other one was upstairs.
她很甜美呢
She was sweet, mmm, mmm, mmm.
我处置了她
I took her out.
那样使你很生气吧
I bet that really pisses you off.
你可能认为我不是个好人
You probably don't think I'm a very nice guy.
是不是？
Do you?
我认为你是人渣
Buddy, I think you're slime.
我就是有这个问题
You see, I got this problem.
警察都不喜欢我，所以我不喜欢警察
Cops don't like me, so I don't like cops.
扶他一把
Well, give the man a hand.
他是你们的了
He's all yours.
- 小心 - 转身
- All right, look out. - Turn around, man.
俊男，这边
Pretty boy, over here.
我没有子弹了
Shit! I'm out of ammo.
我也是
Me, too.
克来伦，他还没死
Hey Clarence, he's still alive.
痛不痛？
Does it hurt? Does it hurt?
好，玩够了
Okay, fun's over.
我们走吧
Okay, let's get out of here.
英伟的王子，晚安
Good night, sweet prince.
等等我…
Hey, wait up, wait up, wait up.
摩菲
Murphy-
抬他过来
Get him over. Lift!
给他氧气罩
Get the ventilator.
推他到四号手术室
Put him in OR 4.
小心，转弯
Easy, easy. Turn.
慢一点
Slow it down now. Slow it down, slow it down.
打开门
Okay, hit the door.
我来量血压
Let me get pressure.
给他氧气罩
Mask him.
血压六十
Got a pressure of 60 palp.
要给他插喉
All right, we have to intubate this guy.
进行环状软骨压迫
Apply cricoid pressure.
放进去了，可有呼吸声？
Okay. All right, I got it in. Breath sounds.
- 行了 - 另一边
- You're in. - Other side.
装起保护设备
Okay, let's go ahead and get the MAST trousers up.
脱掉衣服
Let's get the clothes off.
衣服脱掉，准备检查中枢神经
Okay, clothes off. Let's prep him for a central line.
抽一点血，验血型，要六个单位
Let's get some blood drawn. Type and crossing, six units.
血压正在下降
His pressure's dropping.
中枢神经有反应
Okay, I've got a central line in.
血压恢复，注入盐水
I'm getting pressure back. Normal saline.
爸爸，你做得到吗？
Can you do that, Dad?
TJ里查 - 今晚8点
我要告诉你一件事
I really have to tell you something.
- 血压怎样？ - 四十
- What's our blood pressure? - I've got 40 palp.
好的
All right.
V纤维颤动要用震荡器
Coarse V-Fib. Okay, we got to shock him.
使用苏醒袋
Let's get the Ambu bag.
放进佛利器
Clear the patches.
拿走保护设备
Put the Foley in.
准备电击
Let's go ahead and blow his MAST trousers.
退后
Stand clear.
退后，电击
Stand clear. Shock him.
好的
All right.
V纤维颤动，再震他
Coarse V-Fib. Let's shock him again.
退后
Clear.
好
All right.
没反应，来吧，注射强心剂
Flatline. Let's go intracardiac epinephrine.
来了
Let's go.
好
Okay.
好，注射了
All right, it's in.
没有脉搏
There's no pulse.
再震动一次，没反应就放弃吧
All right, let's go ahead and shock a flat line, and let's quit.
好的，大家退后
Okay, everybody, clear!
退后
Stand clear.
行了，我们已经尽力了
All right, I think that's all we can do.
算了吧，死亡时间？
Let's call it. What's the time?
6点15分
6:15.
6点15分正
Sharp.
开始启动了
No, it's starting to roll.
还是开的
Still rolling.
- 该死！ - 不
- Shit! - Nope.
让我看看
Let me see.
拿发光二极管来
Bring in the L.E.D.
锁好它
Let's lock it down.
- 他启动了 - 情况怎样？
- He's on. - What's the story?
我们保住了左手臂
We were able to save the left arm.
什么？我们说好了，全身装假肢的
What? I thought we agreed on total body prosthesis.
- 割掉那只手臂 - 天，莫顿
- Now, lose the arm, okay? - Jesus, Morton.
他能理解吗？
Can he understand what I'm saying?
我们反正会洗掉他的记忆
It doesn't matter. We're gonna blank his memory, anyway.
我们该割掉那只手臂，你认为怎样？
Well, I think we should lose the arm. What do you think, Johnson?
他加入警队时签了弃权书
Well, he signed the release forms when he joined the force.
况且他已经死了 我们可以随意处置的
He's legally dead. We can do pretty much what we want to.
割掉那只手臂
Lose the arm.
关掉他，准备进行手术
Shut him down. Prep him for surgery.
表皮会是这样的
The entire outer skin will be like this.
是钦金属，铺上合成纤维
It's titanium laminated with Kevlar.
来，跟他握手
Go ahead. Shake his hand.
你经常来这里？你好吗？
Come here often? How you doing?
天啊！
Oh, God!
握得真有力
He's got a hell of a grip.
那有四百磅 他可以握碎你每一寸骨头
It's 400 foot-pounds. He could crush every bone in your hand.
好了，将它接在肩膀上
All right. Attach it to his shoulder.
我喜欢呢
I like that.
你会是个大混蛋
You are gonna be a bad motherfucker.
指令，下载记忆
看，他望着我们
Hey, look, look! He's watching us!
你好吗？
How you doing?
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi! - Hi!
新年快乐
Happy new year!
这是给你的
This is for you.
新年快乐
Happy new year.
我们是两者兼得的
We get the best of both worlds.
现在最快速的…
The fastest reflexes modern technology has to offer,
计算机记忆反应
onboard computer-assisted memory,
和永久的警察巡逻计划
and a lifetime of on-the-street law enforcement programming.
我很高兴为大家介绍…
It is my great pleasure to present to you,
机器战警
Robocop.
来吧
Come on, come on, come on.
这是为你而设的，给你的，来吧
Come on. That's for you. That's for you.
去吧
Go, Robo.
我是你们所谓的惯犯
I am what you call a repeat offender.
我会再犯罪的
I repeat, I will offend again.
我受最高指示
I get my orders from a higher source.
闭嘴，混蛋
Shut up, asshole.
你妈知道你是这样讲话的吗？
Does your mother know you talk like that?
靠旁边进去
Bring him in through the side door.
已设了一间房间作观察
This holding cell has been set up for observation.
看起来很棒
Looks perfect.
- 这是怎么一回事？ - 他是谁
- What is this all about? - Who is this guy?
- 约翰瑞德警官 - 这是怎么回事？
- Sergeant John Reed. - What's this all about?
这是OCP的公事，所以麻烦你走开
It's about official OCP business. So please, get lost.
我们有四、五天…
I think we've got four or five days setup...
胡说八道，我只听从…
Hey, this is bullshit! I take my orders from...
这是什么鬼？
What is this shit?
问得好
Yeah, good question.
- 嘿，等等我 - 去看看
- Hey, wait for me, partner. - Let's go.
他们在那里
There they are.
走
Go.
休息时你会坐在椅子上
When you are at rest, you will sit in the chair.
我明白
Yes. I understand.
追踪又怎样？
What about tracking?
我们用这个来追踪他的位置
We can check his exact location at all times with one of these.
他怎样进食？
How does he eat?
他的消化系统很简单
His digestive system is extremely simple.
这个处理器配制出一种浆糊
This processor dispenses a rudimentary paste
维持他的生理系统
that sustains his organic system.
味道好像婴儿食物
Tastes like baby food.
好好享受吧
Knock yourself out.
我们先从追踪开始
Okay, let's start with tracking.
- 给我一个方位 - 收到吗？
- Give me a grid. - Got it.
清楚
There.
- 目标 - 清楚
- Target? - Check.
瞄准中
- 目标 - 清楚
- Target. - Check.
现在跟着
Now follow.
清楚
Check.
- 声音重量分析器，一、二… - 启动了
Voice stress analyzer, one, two...
三
- ...three. - Ahhh.
- 清楚 - 记录
- Check. - Record. Ahhh.
- 回放 - 加强至一半
- Now playback. - Bring it up 50%.
回放
- 回放 - 加强至一半
- Now playback. - Bring it up 50%.
全画面
Give me a full frame.
- 他准备好了 - 好，让开
- We got it. - All right, clear out.
你的最高指令是什么？
What are your prime directives?
服务大众、保护无辜者、执行法纪
Serve the public trust, protect the innocent, uphold the law.
一：取得公众信任 二：保护无辜者
三：执行法纪
很好
That's good.
非常好
That's very good.
指令四：机密
我爱死那个家伙
I fucking love that guy!
是超级警察
Hey, Lewis, it's Supercop.
看那支手枪
Look at that fucking gun.
妈的！
Shit!
- 这家伙很出色 - 他不是人，是机器
- This guy's really good. - He's not a guy. He's a machine.
他们想怎样？取代我们？
What are they gonna do, replace us?
来吧
Come on.
底特律警察局
- 瑞德 - 是
- Reed. - Yeah?
他要一辆车
He needs a car.
谢谢你
Thank you.
好的，不用客气
Sure. Anytime.
去对付他们吧
Oh, yeah. Go get 'em, boy!
付多少钱我也愿意
I'd buy that for a dollar!
比比，生日快乐
先生，还有什么需要？
Will there be anything else, sir?
把收款机的钱全放进袋子里
Yeah, empty the register and put the money in the bag.
什么？
Excuse me?
我说把所有的钱给我，别跟我耍花招
I said give me your money and all of it, and don't fuck with me!
快点
Now move!
老头，打开保险箱
Open the safe, Pops.
打开保险箱！
Open the goddamn safe!
我们没有保险箱
We don't have a safe.
该死！你的保险箱在那里，快打开它
Shit! There's your goddamn safe! Open that son of a bitch!
别拖延，快打开那个东西！
Quit stalling, man! I'm gonna count to three! You better open that son of a bitch.
快点
Come on! Come on!
我会干掉她的
I'm gonna blow her brains out.
- 我会打开保险箱 - 乖
- I'll open the safe. - Good boy.
快点
Come on.
我数三声你就要打开它
Well, you better open that on the count of three.
一、二…
One, two...
他妈的
Fuck me.
放下那支枪，你被拘捕了
Drop the gun. You are under arrest.
去你的！
Fuck me! Fuck me!
Fuck me!
谢谢你合作，晚安
Thank you for your cooperation. Good night.
付多少钱我也愿意！
I'll buy that for a dollar!
第三街及拿许路有罪案发生
求你们不要！别碰我！走开
Don't touch me! Get away! Get away!
我们不要你的钱！
We don't want your bag!
我们要你
We want you!
放松点，我们不想伤害你
Take it easy! We don't want to hurt you!
太多头发了
That's too much hair.
对，我们替她剪发
I know, we'll give her a haircut!
- 嘿 - 什么？
- Hey, hey. - What?
下面有更多毛发呢！
There's more hair down there!
不要！
No, don't!
求求你
Please!
不要！
No!
救命！
Help me!
救救我！
放开那个女人，你们被拘捕了
Let the woman go. You are under arrest.
该死
Shit!
老兄，你还是退后
You better back up, pal!
因为他要干她！
'Cause, he's gonna kill her!
他要杀死她
He's gonna kill her!
你这妹子！
You fucking bitch!
他要杀死她！
He's gonna kill her, man!
He's gonna kill her!
到你了，变态鬼
Your move, creep.
不要紧
Okay!
没事的
It's okay!
谢天谢地
吓死我了，谢谢你
I was so scared. Thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
太太，你受惊了
Madam, you have suffered an emotional shock.
我会通知一个强奸危机应变中心
I will notify a rape crisis center.
所有单位，第六区，请封锁交汇处
All units, Sector 6, please close intersections...
我不管，赶那些人去楼梯边
I don't care. Get those men by the stairs now!
快去！
Hit it!
本市政府从不着重应付恐怖活动
Terrorism has never been a factor in city politics before.
今天情况有变了，因为前议员密朗…
But that changed today when former city councilman Ron Miller
持枪闯进了大会堂
entered City Hall with a gun.
他在二楼
He's now on the second floor
挟持着吉布森市长和他的下属作人质
holding Mayor Gibson and his staff hostage.
我们相信密朗已经杀死其中一名人质
We do believe that Miller has killed one of the hostages.
长官，下一步怎样做？
Lieutenant, what's next?
等候，恐怖活动很棘手的
We wait. Terrorism is a very tricky business.
立刻作大规模反击是上策
Maximum and immediate retaliation is the best policy.
可惜…
But unfortunately...
对不起
Excuse us.
等一下，你们去哪里？
Where are you going?
请发表一下
Statement, please.
我们要控制人群，叫那些人退后
Let's have some crowd control! Come on, get these people back!
你去哪里？
Where the hell do you think you're going?
叫他继续谈话
Keep him talking.
有一个问题
谁制造你的？
Who made you?
你是否战无不胜？
Are you invincible?
密朗，不要伤害市长 我们会答应你所有的要求
Okay, Miller, don't hurt the Mayor. We'll give you whatever you want.
第一，不要耍我，我是拚了命的
First, don't fuck with me! I'm a desperate man!
第二，我要一些新鲜咖啡
And second, I want some fresh coffee!
第三，我要重新点票
And third, I want a recount!
不管结果如何，我要恢复职位
And no matter how it turns out, I want my old job back!
好的
Okay.
我还要一个更大的办公室
And I want a bigger office!
还要一辆新车
And I want a new car!
全部由市政府支付
And I want the City to pay for it all!
要哪款车？
What kind of car, Miller?
要有真皮活动座位…
Something with reclining leather seats,
要快速和费油量的
that goes really fast and gets really shitty gas mileage!
6000 SUX型好吗？
How about the 6000 SUX?
好，可以的
Yeah! Okay, sure!
它有没有速度调节的？
What about cruise control? Does it come with cruise control?
没问题，放走市长吧 我们还可以送你汽车音响
Hey, no problem, Miller. Let the Mayor go, we'll even throw in a Blaupunkt.
警官，不要耍我
Lieutenant, don't jerk me off!
人家耍我时我会杀了他们
When people jerk me off, I kill them!
你要看看吗？
You want to see?
热能录像
市长，站起来！
Get up, Your Honor, get up. Get up!
站起来，你的市民想看看你
Your public wants to see you!
从没有人认真对待我
Nobody ever takes me seriously!
我们现在认真一点
We'll get serious now!
跟市长道别吧！
And kiss the Mayor's ass good-bye!
机器战警是谁？他是谁？
Robocop. Who is he?
他是什么？他从何而来？
What is he? Where does he come from?
他是OCP革命性的…
He's OCP's newest soldier
罪案管理计划的最新战士
in their revolutionary crime management program.
OCP发言人声称这具无畏的机器
OCP Spokesmen claim that the fearless machine
令底特律旧城的匪徒闻风丧胆
has crooks on the run in Old Detroit.
今天，艾亚科卡小学的学生可一睹…
Today, kids at Lee lacocca Elementary School got to meet in person
他们父母只能在漫画看到的人物
what their parents only read about in comic books.
对不起，机械人，有什么特别讯息
Robo, excuse me, Robo. Any special message
给在家中收看的孩子们吗？
for all the kids watching at home?
不要惹上麻烦
Stay out of trouble.
墨西哥危机再度升级
More fighting in the Mexican crisis today
美军和墨西哥国民军连手突击…
when American troops participated in a joint raid with Mexican nationals
对付部署在阿科普科的叛军火箭
against rebel rocket positions in Acapulco.
现在请看这个
Now this.
红色警报…
Red alert. Red alert. Red alert.
你越过了我的死亡界线
You crossed my line of death.
你没有拆掉你的MX武器
You haven't dismantled your MX stockpile.
巴基斯坦威胁着我的边境
Pakistan is threatening my border.
就是这样，不可再有军事援助
That's it, buster. No more military aid.
核武大战，快从速装置
Nukem, get them before they get you.
核武大战
毕氏兄弟出品的 另一优质家庭游戏
今天劳工领袖都同意
Today, labor leaders agreed to sanction construction
支持兴建OCP的三角洲城
of OCP's Delta City,
此举会制造一百万个新职位
thereby creating an estimated one million much-needed new jobs,
尽管在危险的旧城区 工人的安全仍成疑问
despite questions about worker safety in dangerous Old Detroit.
OCP保安概念部副总裁罗伯莫顿
Robort Morton, vice president, Security Concepts, OCP.
我不能对三角洲城置评
I'm afraid I can't comment on Delta City.
但我可以告诉大家以下的消息
That's not my division. But I will tell you this.
罗伯莫顿 - OCP副总裁
保安概念部估计在40天内
At Security Concepts, we're projecting the end of crime
会将旧城区的罪案灭绝
in Old Detroit within 40 days.
本市有一个新家伙，他名叫机器战警
There's a new guy in town. His name's Robocop.
伯仔…副总裁，恭喜你
Hey, hey, hey. Bobby boy. Vice president. Congratulations.
周二晚玩手球吗？
Handball Tuesday night?
我想的…
Bill, I'd love to. But I got a date.
但我请了一些模特儿来我家
Couple models coming over to my place. Know what I mean?
付多少钱我也愿意
I'd buy that for a dollar.
罗伯，欢迎加入
Welcome to the club, Bob.
…那是真的
...and that's a true story.
你借着机器战警 在保安概念部声名大噪了
Making a real name for yourself in Security Concepts with Robocop.
我尽力了
I try.
告诉我一些底细吧
I'm in on the bottom line, pal.
听说琼斯很生气
I hear Jones was plenty pissed.
他有这个杀手人物，但那是个烟幕
Oh, you know, he's got this killer rep, but it's a smokescreen.
他是只无牙老虎，是个胆小鬼
Let's face it, he's lost his teeth. The guy's a pussy.
我们是否说着同一个迪克琼斯？
Are we talking about the same Dick Jones?
他年老，我们年轻，人生就是那样
Hey, he's old, we're young, and that's life.
我要…
I got to...
我要走了，要开会
I got to go. I got a meeting.
罗伯，恭喜你
Congratulations, Bob.
谢谢
Thanks.
我记得我在这间公司 做初级行政人员时…
I remember when I was a young executive for this company.
我们给老板取了一些花名
I used to call the old man funny names.
铁屁股
Iron Butt,
蠢蛋
Boner.
有一次我甚至叫他做…混蛋
Once, I even called him asshole.
但永远尊敬着他
But there was always respect.
我永远知道在哪里定下底线
I always knew where the line was drawn.
你却越过它了
And you just stepped over it, buddy boy.
你侮辱了我
You've insulted me, and you've insulted this company
你的混账创作也侮辱了这间公司
with that bastard creation of yours!
我有印209的军事售卖保证
I had a guaranteed military sale with Ed 209!
革新计划，售卖零件25年
Renovation program. Spare parts for 25 years.
管创于不行？
Who cares if it worked or not?
老板认为这件事很重要
The old man thought it was pretty important,
迪克
Dick.
你知道吗？他是个老好人
You know, he's a sweet old man.
他也是出于好意
And he means well.
但他不是长生不老的
But he's not going to live forever.
我是这里的第二号总管
And I'm number two around here.
简单的数学，是不是？
Pretty simple math, huh, Bob?
你是…
You just
针对错人了
fucked with the wrong guy.
你发疯了
You're out of your fucking mind.
你最好求神拜佛…
You better pray
你那个怪物不会出差错
that that unholy monster of yours doesn't screw up.
- 你饿吗？ - 不，谢谢
- You hungry? - No, thanks.
不好了
No.
那些该死的叛军炸毁了阿科普科机场
Goddamn rebels blew up the airport in Acapulco yesterday.
倒霉，我们下周要去那里 那是什么？
Great. We were going there next week. Wait, what was that?
看，拼命小子启动了
Hey, look! Bucket boy's online.
你…
停下，别走，等一会！
Halt. Stop! Wait a minute!
什么事？
What the hell's going on?
- 不知道，他刚走了 - 他走了？
- I don't know. He just left. - Just left?
罗士福！
Roosevelt!
我们有麻烦
Rosie, we got a problem.
让开
Out of the way!
看这个
Take a look at this.
该死！找罗伯莫顿
Shit! Call Bob Morton!
杰利，逮捕他，我稍后回来
Jerry, book him. I'll catch up with you later.
你好，我没有机会好好地自我介绍
Hello. I haven't really had a chance to introduce myself.
我是安妮陆逸斯
I'm Anne Lewis.
你有名字吗？
Do you have a name?
陆逸斯警员，有什么可以效劳？
How can I help you, Officer Lewis?
我不是那个意思，你没有名字的吗？
That's not really what I meant. Don't you have a name?
别动，在这里签名
Hold it. Just sign right here, sir.
你不明白，我是OCP的
You don't understand. I'm OCP.
摩菲，是你
Murphy, it's you.
你真的不记得我？
You really don't remember me, do you?
对不起
Excuse me.
我要走了
I have to go.
总有地方会发生罪案的
Somewhere there is a crime happening.
停下来！
Stop!
你跟他说了什么？
What did you talk to him about? What did you say?
- 没什么 - 该死
- Nothing. - Shit.
该死
Shit.
别走！
Stop!
你别走！
You there, stop!
你有麻烦了，警员，走吧
You're in a lot of trouble, Officer! Come on!
这间警察局答应全面合作的
I was assured full cooperation by this precinct, buddy,
你的手下弄坏了事情
and if it gets screwed up by one of your grunts,
我会开除你
I'm gonna have your job.
- 最新情况怎样？ - 不清楚
- What's the update? - It's hard to be 100%.
是否有故障？
We have a glitch or what?
他没有躯体反应设计的
This system was never designed to experience detailed somatic response.
他做了一个梦
He had a dream, a dream.
- 这个警员查问过他 - 我没有查问他
- This cop saw fit to question him. - I didn't question him.
我问他的名字，他不知道
I asked him his name. He didn't know.
好极了，让我们说清楚
Great. Let me make it real clear for you.
他没有名字，他只是个程序
He doesn't have a name. He's got a program.
他是个产品，明白吗？
He's product. Is that clear?
明白
Sure.
抓他回来进行全套系统机件检查
I say we pull him in, run a systems check, the works.
可能需要花七到十天
Take a week. Maybe 10 days.
截断他的能源，因为他做了一个梦？
You want to take him offline because he had a dream?
你说笑吗？
What, are you kidding?
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
- 瑞德，听着 - 是
- Listen, Reed. - Yeah?
记着一件事，这个计划跟警察无关
Try to keep one thing in mind. This project doesn't concern cops.
它是机密的，它是OCP的
It's classified. It's OCP.
你明白吗？
You got it, mister?
我明白
Yeah, I got it.
好
Good.
好，我们让他在街上…
Right, we keep him on the street...
警官，对不起
Sorry, Sarge.
我坏了事
I fucked up.
算了吧，这家伙是个大混蛋
Forget it, kid. This guy's a serious asshole.
24小时营业
书虫，把所有的钱给我 否则我干掉你
Give me all your money, bookworm, or I blow your brains out.
现在给七号加油
Now fill it up on number 7.
别做傻事
Don't do nothing stupid, man.
我是个神枪手
I'm a good shot.
我可以从这里射中你
I could hit you in the eye from here.
正在发生罪案
老哥…你在看什么书？
Hey, man, what you reading in there?
平面几何
你是个大学生？
You a college boy or something?
你一定以为自己很聪明了
I bet you think you're pretty smart?
以为可以敌过子弹？
Think you could outsmart a bullet?
我们看个究竟，好吗？
What do you say we find out?
我在跟你说话，你认为怎样？
I'm talking to you! What do you say?
我在跟你说话！
I'm talking to you!
放下它
Drop it.
不管死活，你也要束手就擒
Dead or alive, you are coming with me.
我知道你是谁
I know you.
拘捕状态
你已经死了
You're dead.
录像中
是我们杀你的
We killed you!
回放
你已经死了
You're dead.
是我们杀你的
We killed you!
你是谁？
Who are you?
杰利，看谁来了
Jerry, Jerry. Look who it is.
有什么可以效劳？
Can I help you, sir?
- 没有 - 你到底想怎样？
- No. - What is it exactly that you want?
你…你不能进入这里
You can't enter here! Wait a second!
等一会…
Just a minute!
这里是禁区
This is a restricted area!
底特律警察局
他进去了
He's in.
罪犯身分资料组
照片身分
输入数据
正在输入数据
搜寻中
符合
安东诺阿苗
已知同党
利昂纳许
乔卡斯
史蒂芬明
鲍迪克来伦
被捕记录：抢劫
贩毒、袭击、强奸
涉嫌谋杀摩菲
摩菲，是你
Murphy, it's you.
摩菲获颁美伦达奖
密芝根州底特律市春花路548号
已经身亡
春花路
春花路548号
春花
出售
欢迎参观
Welcome, shopper.
我们逛逛你的新居吧
Let's take a stroll through your new home.
这是ZM工业建的家庭独立屋
This is a one-family house built by ZEM Industries.
令仔近学校和商店…
Situated near schools and shopping centers,
这个先进的发展区有七倍的增长率
this progressive development has a growth factor of 7.
厉害
Wow.
爸爸，你做得到吗？
Can you do that, Dad?
谁负责在家里煮饭也不要紧
...and, say, it doesn't matter who cooks in your family,
因为这个厨房是由食品概念设计的 使一切都变得容易
because this kitchen by Food Concepts makes everything a snap.
世界级丈夫
爸爸
Dad.
来吧，戴上帽子，他可爱吗？
爸爸，来吧
Come on, Dad. Come on, Dad.
来照相
Get in the picture.
快点
Come on, come on.
我要告诉你一件事
I really have to tell you something.
我爱你
I love you.
主人房
That's the master bedroom.
多用途的空间，设计典雅
A functional space with a touch of elegance.
你考虑好了没有？
Have you thought it all over?
何不给我开一个价钱
Why not make me an offer?
拘捕状态
疑犯利昂纳许
拘捕状态 疑犯利昂纳许
鲍迪克来伦在哪里？
Where is Clarence Boddicker?
好吧
Okay?
- 该死 - 我们谈一下
- Shit! - Let's talk.
混蛋！
Son of a bitch!
它听起来有点特别
There's just something about the way it sounds.
副总裁
Vice president.
令我兴奋极了
It just turns me on.
你们真是了不起
God, you girls are so great.
我喜欢跟聪明的女人在一起
I mean I just... I love to be with intelligent women.
聪明是很性感的
Smart is so sexy.
我知道
I know.
有时候只要我想起一样东西…
Sometimes I could just think of something,
就会令我欲火中烧的
and it could just get me so horny.
浪费脑力是可怕的事
Yeah, well, a mind is a terrible thing to waste.
对
Yeah.
我很容易就觉得无聊
I get bored so easily.
对
Yep.
而且你要很多刺激
And you need lots of stimulation, Bobby.
- 是的，别动 - 我不会的
- Yes, I do. Don't move. - I won't.
罗伯？
Bob?
怎样？
What?
- 罗伯，留一点给我 - 放心吧
- Bob, save some for me. - Don't worry. I'll...
一定是送香槟来，别走开
Must be the champagne. Stay here.
你好吗？
How you doing...
妹子们，走吧
Bitches, leave.
天，罗伯，再见
Gee, Bobby. Bye.
- 你会找我吗？ - 走啦
- You gonna call me? - Come on.
你在干什么？
What the fuck are you doing?
你可知道我是谁？
Do you know who I am?
你以为这件事你可以脱身，那你就…
If you think you're gonna get away with this...
他妈的！
Goddamn it!
停手！你要什么我都给你 求你别杀我
Stop! I'll give you anything you want! Just please, please don't kill me, all right?
你好，小伙子，迪克琼斯在此
Hello, buddy boy. Dick Jones here.
我猜你现在已经跪地求饶 想保住你的性命吧
I guess you're on your knees about now, begging for your life.
真可怜
Pathetic.
你现在不觉得那么意气风发了吧？
You don't feel so cocky now, do you, Bob?
他给你多少钱，我马上双倍给你
Whatever he's paying you, I'll double it right now.
你可知道可悲的是什么？
You know what the tragedy is here, Bob?
我们本可以做朋友
We could have been friends.
但你不肯依循正确途径
But you wouldn't go through proper channels.
你在我头上动土
You went over my head.
那样很痛
That hurt.
但世事如常，这是老生常谈 为爱和光荣奋斗
But life goes on. It's an old story, the fight for love and glory, huh, Bob?
你视它为一场游戏会好一点的
It helps if you think of it as a game, Bob.
每场游戏都有赢家…和输家
Every game has a winner and a loser.
我要你输个精光
I'm cashing you out, Bob.
我们需要更多管子
We need more tubing.
西尔，我不要付那个价钱
I don't think I want to pay you that, Sal.
我不管你要什么，价钱由我来定
I don't give a shit what you want to pay. I set the prices here.
可能你没听清楚 底特律是由我操控的
Listen, pal, maybe you haven't heard. I'm the guy in Old Detroit.
你要在我的市场占位置…
You want space in my marketplace,
就要给我大量折扣
you're gonna have to give me a volume discount.
没有折扣
I'm not into discounts.
乔，给他看看 我们有什么圣诞礼物给他
Joe, show the man what we brought him for Christmas.
考虑一下，发财机会多的是
Think about it, chum. Good business is where you find it.
好吧，让我说个清楚
Okay, let me try to put this in perspective.
你们已经杀了一批警察
You killed a bunch of cops.
听说你们在市区有很多联系
The word around is that you've got a lot of heavy connections downtown.
你令我很多朋友紧张起来
You make a lot of my friends nervous.
有很多人想看到我这样的人…
A lot of people would love to see a guy like me
令你这样的人生意倒闭
put a guy like you out of business.
我不知道，我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
可能我说得不清楚
Maybe I'm just not making myself clear.
我不想耍你
I don't want to fuck with you, Sal.
但我有很多联系，我有销售组织
But I got the connections. I got the sales organization.
我有能力把这间工厂…
I got the muscle to shove enough of this factory
弄得一团糟，你会鸡犬不宁的
so far up your stupid wop ass that you'll shit snow for a year.
法兰基，干掉这个混蛋
Frankie, blow this cocksucker's head off.
枪…
Guns, guns, guns!
别这样
Come on, Sal!
老虎队今晚出赛
The Tigers are playing tonight.
我一场也不会错过的
I never miss a game.
我说笑罢了
Just kidding.
走
Go!
Go.
瞄准中
静静地过来，否则会有麻烦
Come quietly or there will be trouble.
去你的
Fuck you!
该死
鲍迪克来伦，你已经被拘捕
Clarence Boddicker, you are under arrest.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
去你的！
Fuck you!
等一会…
Hey, wait a minute. Wait a minute!
我受保护的，有人保护我
I'm protected, man. I've got protection!
你有权聘请律师
You have the right to an attorney.
这是什么鬼？
What is this shit?
他妈的
Goddamn it.
Goddamn it! Listen to me!
听着，混蛋，是另一个人
Listen to me, you fuck! There's another guy.
他是OCP的高级总裁
He's OCP. He's a senior president.
你所说的话可能会成为呈堂证供
Anything you say may be used against you.
是迪克琼斯！
It's Dick Jones!
你不在乎吗，混蛋？
Don't you get it? You cocksucker!
我替迪克琼斯工作的！迪克琼斯！
I work for Dick Jones. Dick Jones!
他是OCP的第二号总管 OCP是管理警队的
He's the number two guy at OCP. OCP runs the cops!
你是个警察！
You're a cop.
警察…
Cop.
指令三：执行法纪
对，我是个警察
Yes. I am a cop.
拘捕状态
我也不喜欢这样，但听着！
I don't like it any more than you do, Reed, but listen!
你听着，混蛋
You listen to me, you asshole!
你说要关闭一支主要的市区警队
You're talking about shutting down a major metropolitan police force.
没有警察，这个城市会大混乱的
Without cops, this city would tear itself apart.
工会昨晚表决要罢工
The Union thinks you should know there was a strike vote last night.
上周我们死了五个同僚
We lost five guys last week.
我们在外面挨打
We're getting creamed out there, Reed.
逮捕他
Book him.
什么罪名？
What's the charge?
他是杀警凶手
He's a cop killer.
该死！
Shit!
我要打电话
Just give me my fucking phone call.
我明白
I understand.
律师们会在24小时内把你弄出来
Look, the lawyers will have you out in 24 hours.
只要别透露其他事情
Just don't say anything else.
天，你真的弄得一团糟
Jesus, you really screwed up.
回放
鲍迪克来伦 档案编号F5908520492
你不在乎吗？我替迪克琼斯工作的
Don't you get it? I work for Dick Jones!
迪克琼斯
Dick Jones!
我替迪克琼斯工作的
I work for Dick Jones!
他管理OCP , OCP是管理警队
He runs OCP. OCP runs the cops.
进来吧
Come in, Officer.
通常我不接见没有预约的人
You know, I don't usually see anyone without an appointment,
但你是例外
but in your case, I'll make an exception.
你被拘捕了
You are under arrest.
什么罪名？
On what charge?
协助及教唆一名已知的重犯
Aiding and abetting a known felon.
违反处罚规则
听来我有大麻烦了
Sounds like I'm in a lot of trouble.
还是拘捕我好了
You better take me in.
我会的
I Will.
产品违规
指令四
警员，有什么问题？
What's the matter, Officer?
我告诉你有什么问题吧
I'll tell you what's the matter.
这是一项称为指令四的保险政策
It's a little insurance policy called Directive 4.
是我对你的心理状况作出的小贡献
My little contribution to your psychological profile.
只要你企图拘捕OCP高级人员
Any attempt to arrest a senior officer of OCP
都会导致机件停顿
results in shutdown.
你以为是什么？
What did you think?
以为你是个普通的警察？
That you were an ordinary police officer?
你是我们的产品
You're our product.
我们不能让产品造反的
And we can't very well have our products turning against us, can we?
你仍然有点反抗力
Still a little fight left in you.
或许你想见见我一个朋友
Maybe you'd like to meet a friend of mine.
我要杀死罗伯莫顿，因为他犯了错误
I had to kill Bob Morton because he made a mistake.
现在是时候清除那个错误
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
找黑基卡来，大厦里有麻烦
Put Lieutenant Hedgecock on the line. There's trouble in the tower!
准备开火
Prepare to fire.
- 等一下 - 他是个警察
- Hey, wait a second! - He's a cop, for God's sakes!
- 你不能那样做的 - 我们有命令要摧毁它
- Hedgecock! You can't do that! - We have orders to destroy it.
- 该死 - 你们都是疯子
- Oh, shit! - You're maniacs!
随意开火！
Fire at will.
进攻！
Move in.
摩菲！
Murphy!
摩菲，是我
Murphy, it's me.
陆逸斯
Lewis.
下来！
Move down!
到另一层楼
On the next level.
三楼，他在三楼
Lieutenant! Level 3, level 3. He's on level 3!
这边…
Over here! Over here!
开火
Open fire!
它回来了
It's back.
又流行巨大了，因为越大越好
Big is back, because bigger is better.
6000 SUx型号，一个美国传统
6000 SUX.
晚安，我是帕金斯，他是卡西黄
Good evening. I'm Jesse Perkins with Casey Wong.
主要新闻，圣巴巴拉市
Top story, Santa Barbara.
装在战略性防卫和平平台上的 一支激光大炮
10,000 acres of wooded residential land were scorched in an instant
今天进行例行测试时失火…
when a laser cannon aboard the strategic defense peace platform
烧毁了一万亩树茂密树林覆盖的民居
misfired today during routine start-up tests.
卡西
Casey.
已知有113名的死者
Yes, it was a day of mourning for the families of 113 people known dead at this hour,
其中包括两位前总统
among them, two former United States Presidents
他们在圣巴巴拉地区过着退休生活
who had retired in the Santa Barbara area.
是国民哀痛的一天
A day of mourning for a country.
警员工会代表和OCP今天继续谈判
Police union representatives and OCP continue negotiations today
希望避免在明晚午夜举行的…
in hopes of averting a citywide strike by police,
全市警员大罢工
scheduled to begin tomorrow at midnight.
贾斯顿华金斯会有更多报导
Justin Ballard-Watkins has more.
他们仍在执勤，但明天又怎样？
They're still on duty, but what about tomorrow?
我们访问过住在治安恶劣的 勒盛顿区市民
That's the question we put to people in the crime-plagued Lexington area.
他们是公仆，他们有职业保障
They're public servants. They got job security.
彼得维利一屋主
他们不应该罢工
They're not supposed to strike.
这是个自由社会
It's a free society,
奇瓦罗森本一失业人士
但没什么是自由的
except there ain't nothin' free
因为没有保证
'cause there's no guarantees, you know?
你得靠自己
You're on your own.
那是世界的定律
It's the law of the jungle.
小心
Be very careful.
对不起
Excuse me, please.
They must be remodeling.
你好，巴巴拉
Hiya, Barbara.
我要见迪克琼斯
Listen, I'm here to see Dick Jones.
见完之后，我还有空
But when I'm done, I've got some free time.
也许你可以填补空档的
Maybe you could fit me in.
鲍迪先生，他在等你
He's expecting you, Mr. Boddicker.
你可以留着那块口香糖
You can keep the gum.
- 看起来不错 - 那个要量一下
- This looks good. - Get a measurement on that.
川页便拿铁锤来
Bring a hammer, too.
迪克老兄，怎么样？
Hey, Dickie boy. How's tricks?
那东西仍然活着
That thing is still alive.
你说什么？
I don't know what you're talking about.
那个拘捕你 把你打得遍体鳞伤的警察
The police officer who arrested you, the one you spilled your guts to.
看看我的脸
Hey. Take a look at my face, Dick.
他当时想杀我
He was trying to kill me.
他是个机械人，笨蛋
He's a cyborg, you idiot.
他把你说的话录下来了
He recorded every word you said.
他的记忆可以作为证据的
His memory's admissible as evidence.
你牵连了我！
You involved me.
你要杀死它
You're gonna have to kill it.
老总，听着
Listen, chief.
你的公司制造那个鬼东西
Your company built the fucking thing.
现在却要我来应付它？
Now I got to deal with it?
我没时间耍这套
I don't have time for this bullshit.
随便吧
Suit yourself, Clarence.
但三角洲城两个月后就动工
But Delta City begins construction in two months.
会有两百万名工人住在拖车房屋
That's 2 million workers living in trailers.
那就是会有毒品、赌博、卖淫
That means drugs, gambling, prostitution.
是懂得拓展新市场的人的新领域
Virgin territory for the man who knows how to open up new markets.
有一个人可以全权控制它…
One man could control it all,
克来伦
Clarence.
毕竟我们是朋友吧
I guess we're gonna be friends after all,
迪克
Richard.
干掉它
Destroy it.
我需要重型的火力
Gonna need some major firepower.
你可否找到军方武器？
You got access to military weaponry?
我们实际上就是军方
We practically are the military.
你有没有带那支手枪？
Did you bring the gun?
警局里没有人
The precinct was deserted.
今天有一半人都没有上班
Half the force didn't show up for work today.
其他人在午夜都会开始离开
Everyone else walks out at midnight.
我猜我们在罢工
I guess we're on strike.
我不清楚你需要什么 只是随便拿了一些
I wasn't sure what you needed. I sort of grabbed things.
你的手枪
Your gun.
你说要这个？
You asked for this?
我带了一些食物给你
I brought you some food.
不，谢谢，我不饿
No, thank you. I'm not hungry.
你可能不喜欢看到这个的
You may not like what you're going to see.
摩菲，再见到你真好
It's really good to see you again, Murphy.
摩菲有妻儿的，他们在哪里？
Murphy had a wife and son. What happened to them?
丧礼之后…她搬走了
After the funeral, she moved away.
他们去了哪里？
Where did they go?
她以为你死了，所以想重新过生活
She thought you were dead. She started over again.
我感觉到他们
I can feel them.
但我不记得他们
But I can't remember them.
别理会我
Leave me alone.
戴维，生日快乐，她是我送的
Happy birthday, Dave. She's from me.
我可以要你们两个吗？
Well, can I have you both?
- 当然可以，我们试过了 - 当然可以，我们试过了
- Sure. We've had our shots. - Sure. We've had our shots.
付多少钱我也愿意
I'd buy that for a dollar!
阿苗
Hey, Emil.
奇利吧酒店怎样？
How's the Gray Bar Hotel?
不错，他们让我留下那件衬衫
Not bad. They let me keep the shirt.
也没有人搞我
Nobody popped my cherry.
阿苗，好吗？看见你真好
Emil, how you doing, man? Good to see you.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey! Hey! - Hey!
我免费出狱时
First they let me out of jail for free,
在监狱的停车场找到这个
then what do I find in the prison parking lot
一辆全新的6000 SUX型
but a brand new 6000 SUX.
还贴着车厂的标贴
Still got the factory sticker on it!
克来伦！
Clarence.
乔有一辆你那样的车
Joey's got a car just like yours, man.
克来伦，你认为怎样？
Yo, Clarence, what do you think, buddy?
你那里有什么？
What do you got there, Clarence?
等等我
Wait up for me!
新玩具呢，我可以玩吗？
Whoa! A new toy! Can I play?
看这个
Watch this.
等一下…
Wait... Wait a minute, Clarence, Clarence!
该死！
Shit!
他妈的
What the fuck?
- 车子不错呢 - 去你的，克来伦
- Nice car, Joe. - Fuck you, Clarence.
让我试一下
Let me try that.
眼镜蛇火箭炮，最新型的
Cobra Assault Cannon. State of the art. Bang!Bang!
我喜欢！
I like it!
小子，给我
Give it up, faggot. Let a man...
自己买吧
No, butthole! Get your own!
别这样
Come on!
拿另一支枪
Get the other gun, Emil!
车子不安全
No car is safe!
做吧
Do it, Emil!
看这个，你们抬头看！
Heads up, you guys.
他在钢铁厂，我们走吧
He's in the steel mill. Let's go.
好，别闹了，我们要走了
All right, cut the horseshit! We're moving out.
来吧，阿苗，快上车
Come on, Emil! Get your ass in the van!
来吧，笨蛋，快走
Come on, lard ass, let's move it!
走开，变态鬼
I'll get you, faggot!
你干什么？
What are you doing?
我的瞄准系统有点毛病
My targeting system is a little messed up.
我可以帮你吗？
Can I help you?
替我瞄准
Aim for me.
瞄准中
你锁定了没有？
Are you locked in now?
锁定了
Yes.
靠左边一点
A little more to the left.
这里
Here.
我认为很准确
I figure that's dead-on.
过奖
Thank you.
- 好，动手吧 - 来吧，我们杀死他
- All right. Let's do it. - Come on, man, let's smoke him!
拆除组来了，那个混…
The wrecking crew is here! Where is that metallic mother?
别乱来
Zip it up, Emil!
别耍花样，干掉他就是
Nothing fancy. Just kill him.
- 阿苗 - 什么？
Emil, in the van.
上车
你现在应该离开这里
You should get out of here now.
我们是伙伴
Hey, we're partners.
去拿车
Get the car.
他妈的
Damn it! Shit!
找我吗？
Looking for me?
干掉他！
Cut him off! Come on!
来吧，快点干掉他
Go on, cut him off!
去
Go, go!
好，你死定了
Okay! Now I got you!
有毒废料
该死
Shit!
救我
Help me.
别碰我
Don't touch me, man!
救我
Help me.
天啊
God!
该死
Shit!
再见了
Bye-bye, baby.
克来伦！
Clarence!
好吧
Okay.
我放弃
I give up.
我不会再拘捕你
I'm not arresting you anymore.
等一会
Now, wait a second.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你把这件事看成是私人恩怨
You're taking this kind of personal, aren't you?
别这样，你令我很紧张
Come on, man. Come on, now. You're making me nervous.
你不能这样做的
Come on, you can't do this.
别这样，不要乱来
Come on now! Don't mess around!
嘿！
Hey! Hey!
别耍了
Come on, man, now, don't get cute!
混蛋， 去死吧！
Die, you bastard!
对…
Yeah!
好…
Yeah! All right!
好！
All right!
克来伦 我打中他了
I got him, Clarence! I got him!
再见了 机器战警
Sayonara, Robocop!
陆逸斯
Lewis!
摩菲， 我很糟糕
Murphy, I'm a mess!
他们会把你修好的
They'll fix you.
他们懂得修好一切
They fix everything.
警察罢工对我们有利
The police strike could really work for us.
我们可以调派ED209到全市各个角落
By the end of the week, we can have Ed 209s in place all over the city
还会马上得到公众支持
and expect immediate public support.
我现在就有一个在楼下 守卫着这幢大厦
I've got one downstairs guarding the building now.
你在私人物业范围非法停车
You are illegally parked on private property.
你有二十秒时间开走你的车辆
You have 20 seconds to move your vehicle.
不管发生什么事情…
...because whatever happens,
本公司都会实践它的指导原则
this corporation will live up to the guiding principles of its founder.
勇气、力量、定罪
Courage, strength, conviction.
我们会以同样积极的态度 面对每个新挑战
We will meet each new challenge with the same aggressive attitude.
那是什么？
What is it?
不知道
I don't know.
警员，我们有何效劳？
How can we help you, Officer?
迪克琼斯以谋杀罪被通缉
Dick Jones is wanted for murder.
指令四
This is absurd!
荒谬，那东西是个暴力的机械神经汉
That thing is a violent mechanical psychopath.
我的程序不容许我对付本公司的人员
My program will not allow me to act against an officer of this company.
这些是严重的指控，你有什么证据？
These are serious charges. What is your evidence?
我要杀死罗伯莫顿，因为他犯了错误
I had to kill Bob Morton because he made a mistake.
现在是时候消除那个错误
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
我要杀死罗伯莫顿，因为他犯了错误
I had to kill Bob Morton because he made a mistake.
现在是时候消除那个错误
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
他有枪
He's got a gun!
起来
Get up!
我马上要一架直升机
I want a chopper. Now!
我们冷静地步上天台
We will walk to the roof very calmly.
我会连同人质登上直升机
I will board the chopper with my hostage.
谁想阻止我…
Anybody tries to stop me,
这个老头就没命
the old geezer gets it.
迪克，你被开除了
Dick, you're fired!
谢谢你
Thank you.
好身手，你叫什么名字？
Nice shooting, son. What's your name?
摩菲
Murphy.